Sup, nerds! Gobo here!
Here's a recap of
everything that's happened so far!
Who are you even talking to?
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
It all began on June 5,
with a mysterious message that appeared
before Saneatsu Narita as he was in class...
Two left
You are currently looking
at this screen
What ensued the next day was a series
of sudden massive fatalities all over the globe.
Social infrastructure came to a halt.
After receiving a call from his friend,
Kazuhiko, Saneatsu made his way to school.
The following day,
a mysterious figure calling themselves
the Emperor appeared,
Tasuketsu
announcing a cruel death game
of majorities called "Tasuketsu".
The whole world was forced to participate.
Participants couldn't choose their responses.
Absent
Their only option was to submit
questions within daily Designated Areas.
The Emperor would select among
the submissions and conduct a tally.
Suginami Ward
Man, all of it was so unfair,
I felt so helpless and hid myself away.
Until I met Ippy-hiko and the guys, that is.
June 5
Two left
You are currently looking
at this screen
June 6
One left
Japanese citizens living
in Tokyo Prefecture
June 7
Zero left
Test run complete
Rules will be announced
tonight at 23:40
June 8
Tasuketsu
Official Start
The Rights
Prime Right                                    Right
The Emperor blabbed on about "making
good use" of Rights and Prime Rights
and scattered 65 envelopes
containing either of the two.
Prime Right                     Right
As for what was inside...
Nishime, take it away!
You're making me explain?!
I mean, you're an adult! 21 years old, right?
I'm still in 8th grade, ya know.
Make it easy and concise, will ya?
I'm not sure age is the issue here...
Fine, if I have to...
Prime Rights are extremely
powerful magical powers.
But obtaining one requires
the sacrifice a human body part.
For example, Omi lost
hearing in his right ear,
Shinozaki lost his right eyesight,
and Rika Suzuki lost her right leg.
Right
Rights, on the other hand,
don't require any sacrifices.
While less enforceable and powerful than Prime
Rights, they can be effective if used right.
Die
According to a woman named Miwa Isshiki,
the Rights fall under three attributes:
Permission, Transmutation, and Production.
Permission
Transmutation
Production
Permission Attribute: Rights that
exercise powers relating to approval.
Some examples include the
Rejection Right and Compliance Right.
My Presentation Right falls under
the Permission Attribute, too!
Transmutation Attribute: Rights that
bring about certain changes or phenomena.
Permission
Transmutation
Production
Examples include Ryuta's Fusion Right
and Shinozaki's Visualization Right.
Permission
Transmutation
Production
Production Attribute: Prime
Rights that produce phenomena
that far surpass those of
the Transmutation Attribute.
Like Souma's Materialization Right!
His powers are crazy!
However, Rights under the
Production Attribute come with risks.
They require the user to announce
their Prime Right with each use.
And it drains a huge amount of energy.
Souma looks exhausted after every use...
Exclusive Prime Right
And finally, what's referred to
as the "Exclusive Prime Right".
Parental                                          Authority
The Prime Right of Parental Authority
apparently belonged to Saneatsu, but...
who knows where he's at right now...
The strongest Prime Rights are under
the Permission Attribute, ya know!
Omi's quasi-major Prime Right of Rejection
and the major Prime Right of Obedience!
When Tasuketsu killed off all the men,
Omi used his Rejection Right to survive,
then submitted a question to revive us
so we could make it out alive.
At this point, it was midnight on June 10.
There were 2.21 million survivors in Tokyo.
The group then went on to gain
new members and work together
to move closer to beating the Emperor
and ending Tasuketsu.
And finally...
June 13
23:30 PM.
Feint Operation!
Emperor Assassination Strategy
Power Station Invasion Operation!
Commence
As of this moment,
Tasuketsu has concluded.
It came with a huge price,
but we were able to defeat the Emperor,
and Tasuketsu came to a close.
As of this moment, Tasuketsu has concluded.
Remaining human
population
1 million people
in the greater
Tokyo area
Rights with unknown          whereabouts
40 Rights
Civilization Maintenance
& Infrastructure
Collapsed
There's a lot of blackouts, but
we still have electricity and water.
The phone lines are down...
same with the internet.
The only reception we get are
one-way transmissions from the Emperor.
But... the radio still works.
There was that one weird transmission
in code... something about "NS" and "FS".
So I could use radio waves if I wanted to.
I think I just got an idea!
My Queen, Lady Kisaragi.
We are nearing distribution time
for the Emperor's message,
so I turned on the in-house power generators.
How many times must I tell you?
The electricity isn't just for distribution
of the fake Emperor's messages.
At the very least, this room where I reign
should be able to use electricity at all hours.
As you wish...
Besides, it's too soon
for the title of "Queen."
I cannot become the ruler
until I lay the Emperor to rest.
Hikari coming in with the regular update.
Lots of weird stuff but
nothing out of the ordinary.
Roger that.
So...
What did you want to talk about, Gobo?
I want to leave Tokyo.
What?! Is your head screwed on right?!
What do you wanna leave Tokyo for?!
Talking with Nishime got me thinking...
It's already been a month
since Tasuketsu ended.
There's no more food left in Tokyo.
Our only path to survival is to escape Tokyo
and make our way around Japan to find food.
But what will happen
if we just up and leave?
It'll be the end of Tokyo for real this time!
You have a point...
Electricity supply is maintained by
Souma's materialized beasts right now.
Without Souma, electricity supply in Tokyo
will come to a complete halt.
Meaning it'd be
a lost civilization, literally.
But think about it...
Where are we headed right now?
Preserving the peace is great and all,
but how long are we gonna
pretend to be the Emperor?
After looking back on everything,
I'm not sure what's right anymore.
"Defeat the Emperor."
I suppose the only thing propelling us
forward was that shared mission...
But without a tangible goal,
we're all left simply exhausted.
Perhaps this is the end of the road...
Hey, Gobo! We've got an
incoming signal from tablet D!
D? It's Ryuta!
There! That should send the signal to Gobo!
Mm-yup!
Looks like they're working hard every night.
I hope they're holding up okay.
I can't wait to finally
talk face-to-face again!
Jeez, you two are as carefree as ever.
You think so?
Mm-ya?
Well, we've got all this to take home.
That should make them happy.
Let's take flowers to Saneatsu
up in the tower, too.
Yeah, let's do that.
Umm... Yeah, about that...
Weren't they left up there in the tower?
Are you sure they haven't decomposed by now?
Don't tell me you forgot...
W-What's wrong, Gobo?
Don't just sit there in silence, you dummy!
Ryuta and the guys are coming back!
Omi and Rika are doing okay too! For real!
Yay! So we get to see them again?!
C'mon! Not in front of—
And they're bringing food too!
There aren't many people in the countryside,
so they haven't touched
the preserved foods yet.
They're bringing fresh vegetables
from farms, too!
T-They're heroes! Thank God!
And...
They found a clue on what to do next!
L-Looks like we survived for good reason.
So things should look up!
No way! We only have five minutes until
today's Emperor announcement, for real!
This is a tablet for outgoing
communication. Where's my laptop?!
Shoot, I left it charging in the basement!
This pair just can't get it together.
Can't be helped! We'll use the TV screen!
Nishime, turn on the switch!
Roger that!
Will they make it in time?
Well... worst case scenario, we could
just say there's no announcement today.
Come on, guys! Somebody
come up with a message, for real!
I can only come up with
inappropriate jokes under pressure!
That's why I'm saying, why not just skip—
Good evening, this is your Emperor.
Time to announce today's results.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
He's back from the dead?
This can't be real!
W-What do we do now?!
That's impossible... we defeated the Emperor!
Calm down!
This isn't necessarily the Emperor.
And it hasn't come up on our phones!
Which means...
It's a TV broadcast?
That's it! Display each station's
broadcast screen!
Nishime! Turn on the other TVs!
It's only on TSK Broadcasting?!
Yeah...
What the hell is going on?
Hey, what about our announcement?
Shoot!
So no usual Emperor announcement today...
Just as I thought.
The current Emperor saw
the television broadcast tonight.
And they canceled the usual announcement...
TSK Broadcasting
Our City of Tokyo
This proves that the
current Emperor is in Tokyo.
Like I thought, this Emperor is different
from the one that conducted Tasuketsu.
I only broadcast from here
at TSK Broadcasting.
As long as they notice that,
they'll make a move for sure.
Until then, I'll keep this up
for as many days as it takes.
Emperor?!
Welcome to TSK Broadcasting!
Just kidding. No way they'd be that quick.
I'll be waiting, Emperor.
To hear out your truth.
All right...
I'm sure you guys can guess today's agenda.
And that's the broadcast
from last night, for real!
You know, I have a feeling
we screwed something up...
Screwed up? You saying I should
have my laptop on me at all times?
You're worried about that?!
First and foremost, let's state the obvious.
The Emperor is dead.
As the ones who fought him,
we're the only ones aware of that fact.
It's been a month since then, and...
Good evening, this is your Emperor.
Today's results are as follows.
For now, Gobo is disguised as the Emperor
Today's execution has been determined to be Tamataro Yamada
(age 33), who killed three people in Meguro Ward. Goodbye.
Please bear in mind to refrain from evil,
and work to live as long as possible.
to send out scripted distributions
to maintain the peace.
Please bear in mind to refrain from evil,
and work to live as long as possible.
But after giving it some thought...
it's possible that someone
has caught on to our façade.
As it stands, the current Emperor
executes criminals on a daily basis.
Most people would assume deceiving
the Emperor would result in their execution.
Yet they went through with the broadcast.
You mean they did it because they know?
To top it off, we ended up
skipping our announcement.
We got distracted, and
they probably realized that.
T-That sounds really bad, for real!
What now? Is it something
we can just ignore?
S-Sure, why not? If we keep
ignoring them, I'm sure they'll stop!
The only one who'd get assassinated is you,
being the fake Emperor and all.
Wait! Ignoring is bad news, for real!
Geez, you're so loud you woke me up.
Souma! Shouldn't you get some rest?
Hikari is guarding the area...
Eren's always up in arms about
something, so it can't be helped.
Why didn't you just wake me up,
Shinozaki-san?
I'm your best weapon.
You don't look so well.
Get some more rest.
You've been using your Materialization Right
to the brink every day...
Don't push yourself too hard.
We can't afford to lose either you or Gobo.
The Materialization Right is the source
of all our necessary materials,
and your beasts provide essential labor.
Get as much rest as you need.
I'm the only one who can make it happen.
There's no way I'd give up that easy—
You've got it all wrong, you macho!
You gotta rest for all our sake, idiot!
I hear ya...
Hey Shinozaki-san, I got an idea.
What's that?
Let's cut to the chase.
They purposely broadcast to one station
so we could narrow down
their location, right?
Why not just take the bait and go find them?
But what if it's a trap?
We'll cross that bridge when we get to it.
I can unleash my beast, put
a materialized transceiver on it,
and, if there's any danger, we can
undo the materialization. How's that?
Fine. Let's go to the roof.
I'll take a look at the station
with my Visualization Right.
Sounds good.
Is Souma okay? Like, for real?
The key to information control:
Presentation Right.
Borinmaru Gokokuhotenji
The key to ground search:
Visualization Right.
The key to attack, defense, and
arsenal: Materialization Right.
The key to enforcement: Compliance Right.
This group has all the tools it needs!
My role is to keep things together
so it doesn't fall apart...
I see... they used TV broadcasting.
Yes, my lady.
What an interesting idea.
Very well then...
Let's see now... Okay then...
Looks like I better make sure
that this is real.
How about if I pinch myself?
What's this? A summoning spell?
This feels just as surreal as Tasuketsu...
Or is this the real Emperor?
Shoot, I'm starting to doubt myself.
Wait, something feels off...
Is it not gonna move?
Its hair is flowing but... that's it.
Um, are you the Emperor's pawn?
Well... if I may, I'd like you to take me—
It responded.
I'd like... you to... take me.
So that's what's going on.
It's supposed to guide me
somewhere given my request.
Or at least that's what
it's being commanded to do.
Take
It recognizes that "take" is part of the
command to "take me to a certain place".
Take me to...
But technically, the word "take" by itself
isn't a complete command.
It either responds to a strict set of orders
or it's unable to make its own decisions.
In other words, a complete pawn.
But hang on...
How can it answer my request
to take me somewhere
but have no decision-making abilities?
That would be an oxymoron.
What happens if I were someone dangerous?
If decisions were up to the Emperor,
they would set a transceiver to
monitor me through visuals or audio.
So they set this thing up
just to drop me off...
I'll try messing with them.
Um... Pardon me! Hello, Mr. Emperor!
Can you hear and see me?
Um, as you can see, I'm not armed
and I mean no harm!
Sorry if there was no need for me
to get fully naked... Pardon me.
How did he figure out
there was a transceiver?!
Sounds like he assumes we can see him.
So they're unarmed for sure?
And butt naked. For real.
Um... I plan to head your way now, so...
I guess I'll see you soon?
If you can see through my lie just now,
abandon this beast and send over a second beast.
Once I confirm you've done this, I'll bring you vital information on the Emperor.
I don't sense any danger, do you?
Right. Let's bring him over.
Please take me to where
Mr. Emperor is waiting.
There's a good chance
they have no visual on me.
That means I still have
plenty of opportunities to lie.
Whoa...
This beast has really soft boobs...
Foreboding